{
    "0": [{
        "question": "What is the name of the code entered at the ATM to recive money?",
        "A": "Pin",
        "B": "Code",
        "C": "Number",
        "D": "Spike",
        "correct": "Pin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following can live both in water and on land?",
        "A": "Dog",
        "B": "Frog",
        "C": "Bird",
        "D": "Fish",
        "correct": "Frog"
    },
    {
        "question": "What chemical is added to the water in swimming pools?",
        "A": "Salt",
        "B": "Quicksilver",
        "C": "Ammonia",
        "D": "Chlorine",
        "correct": "Chlorine"
    },
    {
        "question": "A magnet would most likely attract which of the following?",
        "A": "Metal",
        "B": "Plastic",
        "C": "Wood",
        "D": "Glass",
        "correct": "Metal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is the 8 ball in pool?",
        "A": "Green",
        "B": "Black",
        "C": "White",
        "D": "Red",
        "correct": "Black"
    }],
    "1": [{
        "question": "What color are rubies?",
        "A": "White",
        "B": "Blue",
        "C": "Red",
        "D": "Green",
        "correct": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many stars are on the flag of the United States?",
        "A": "50",
        "B": "51",
        "C": "48",
        "D": "37",
        "correct": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a title of a Shakespeare play?",
        "A": "Pamphlet",
        "B": "Porklet",
        "C": "Hamlet",
        "D": "Gimlet",
        "correct": "Hamlet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who created Sherlock Holmes?",
        "A": "Arthur Conan Doyle",
        "B": "Stephen King",
        "C": "J. K. Rowling",
        "D": "Ernest Hemingway",
        "correct": "Arthur Conan Doyle"
    }],
    "2": [{
        "question": "'Zorro' is the Spanish word for what?",
        "A": "Lion",
        "B": "Fox",
        "C": "Rat",
        "D": "Weasel",
        "correct": "Fox"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many X's are there on a regular clock face with Roman numerals?",
        "A": "2",
        "B": "4",
        "C": "5",
        "D": "3",
        "correct": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which among these is not a song sung by Michael Jackson?",
        "A": "Beat it",
        "B": "Billie Jean",
        "C": "Heal the World",
        "D": "Hello",
        "correct": "Hello"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does 'goal in the locker room' mean in football?",
        "A": "Goal at the beginning of the match",
        "B": "Goal at the end of the first half",
        "C": "Off-Goal",
        "D": "Goal kick from the corner",
        "correct": "Goal at the end of the first half"
    }],
    "3": [{
        "question": "The Lemur is native to which country?",
        "A": "South Africa",
        "B": "India",
        "C": "Austria",
        "D": "Madagascar",
        "correct": "Madagascar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which actor won an Academy Award for his role as Forrest Gamp",
        "A": "Kevin Spacey",
        "B": "Alec Baldwin",
        "C": "Tom Hanks",
        "D": "Denzel Washington",
        "correct": "Tom Hanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the smallest country in the world?",
        "A": "Iceland",
        "B": "Seychelles",
        "C": "Spain",
        "D": "Vatican City",
        "correct": "Vatican City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is the nickname for a famous Scottish army regiment?",
        "A": "Black Cat",
        "B": "Black Widow",
        "C": "Black Sea",
        "D": "Black Watch",
        "correct": "Black Watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries have more population than India?",
        "A": "One",
        "B": "Two",
        "C": "Three",
        "D": "Three",
        "correct": "One"
    }],
    "4": [{
        "question": "What skin color are avatars of James Cameron?",
        "A": "Green",
        "B": "Red",
        "C": "Blue",
        "D": "Yellow",
        "correct": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Austria?",
        "A": "Venice",
        "B": "Salzburg",
        "C": "Vienna",
        "D": "Budapest",
        "correct": "Vienna"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sang the song 'We Are The Champions'?",
        "A": "ZZ Top",
        "B": "Backstreet Boys",
        "C": "G Unit",
        "D": "Queen",
        "correct": "Queen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the hottest planet in the solar system?",
        "A": "Venus",
        "B": "Mercury",
        "C": "Jupiter",
        "D": "Mars",
        "correct": "Venus"
    }],
    "5": [{
        "question": "Which scientist won the Nobel Prize in 1922?",
        "A": "E. Fermi",
        "B": "A. Einstein",
        "C": "N. Tesla",
        "D": "I. Newton",
        "correct": "A. Einstein"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which film starred Jhonny Depp?",
        "A": "Mystery Train",
        "B": "Benny and Joon",
        "C": "The Aviator",
        "D": "Untamed Heart",
        "correct": "Benny and Joon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who won the first ever football World Cup?",
        "A": "Uruguay",
        "B": "Brazil",
        "C": "Portugal",
        "D": "Sweden",
        "correct": "Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What geometric shape is generally used for stop signs?",
        "A": "Square",
        "B": "Octagon",
        "C": "Parallelogram",
        "D": "Triangle",
        "correct": "Octagon"
    }],
    "6": [{
        "question": "Who was the first Emperor of Rome?",
        "A": "Romulus",
        "B": "Octavian Augustus",
        "C": "Tiberius",
        "D": "Julius Caesar",
        "correct": "Octavian Augustus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the unit of currency in Irland?",
        "A": "Pound",
        "B": "Lira",
        "C": "Euro",
        "D": "Dollar",
        "correct": "Euro"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 'cynophobia'?",
        "A": "Fear of dogs",
        "B": "Fear of computers",
        "C": "Fear of horses",
        "D": "Fear of blood",
        "correct": "Fear of dogs"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who invented the revolver?",
        "A": "Samuel Colt",
        "B": "Bruce Browning",
        "C": "Dan Wesson",
        "D": "James Revolver",
        "correct": "Samuel Colt"
    }],
    "7": [{
        "question": "In what year was the first iPhone released?",
        "A": "2000",
        "B": "2004",
        "C": "2007",
        "D": "2009",
        "correct": "2007"
    },
    {
        "question": "When playing Blackjack, how many points would be considered a bust?",
        "A": "22",
        "B": "21",
        "C": "15",
        "D": "19",
        "correct": "22"
    },
    {
        "question": "Cambridge Circus is in which UK city?",
        "A": "Oxford",
        "B": "Leeds",
        "C": "Cambridge",
        "D": "London",
        "correct": "London"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to Albert Einstein's famous saying, he does not play dice.",
        "A": "Julius Caesar",
        "B": "Newton",
        "C": "God",
        "D": "Himself",
        "correct": "God"
    }],
    "8": [{
        "question": "What colour were the Pyramids of Giza originally?",
        "A": "Orange",
        "B": "Blue",
        "C": "Pink",
        "D": "White",
        "correct": "White"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many million miles away is the sun from the Earth?",
        "A": "93 million",
        "B": "12 million",
        "C": "136 million",
        "D": "200 million",
        "correct": "93 million"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the first man to orbit the Earth?",
        "A": "John Glenn",
        "B": "Sergei Korolev",
        "C": "Yuri Gagarin",
        "D": "Michael Collins",
        "correct": "Yuri Gagarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who invented Coca-Cola?",
        "A": "Angelo Mariani",
        "B": "Asa Griger Candler",
        "C": "Caleb Bradham",
        "D": "John S. Pemberton",
        "correct": "John S. Pemberton"
    }],
    "9": [{
        "question": "If you asked for 'escargots' in a French restaurant what would you receive?" ,
        "A": "Frogs' legs",
        "B": "Truffles",
        "C": "Snails",
        "D": "Onions",
        "correct": "Snails"
    },
    {
        "question": "When you cut into an onion, which element causes it to smell?",
        "A": "Plutonium",
        "B": "Potassium",
        "C": "Sulfur",
        "D": "Hydrogen",
        "correct": "Sulfur"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the largest ocean on earth?",
        "A": "Pacific Ocean",
        "B": "Atlantic Ocean",
        "C": "Indian Ocean",
        "D": "Arctic Ocean",
        "correct": "Pacific Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year did Hillary Clinton become the 67th Secretary of State of the U.S.A.?",
        "A": "2003",
        "B": "2006",
        "C": "2009",
        "D": "2012",
        "correct": "2009"
    }],
    "10": [{
        "question": "Leo Tolstoy's title was what?",
        "A": "Duke",
        "B": "Cavalier",
        "C": "Count",
        "D": "Prince",
        "correct": "Count"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sport did Alan Shepard play on the moon while there in 1971?",
        "A": "Golf",
        "B": "Shot put",
        "C": "Pole vault",
        "D": "Hurdles",
        "correct": "Golf"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is meant by the Estonian geographical names Hiiumaa and Saaremaa?",
        "A": "Cities",
        "B": "Islands",
        "C": "Lakes",
        "D": "Rivers",
        "correct": "Islands"
    }],
    "11": [{
        "question": "Who was the youngest British Prime Minister?",
        "A": "David Cameron",
        "B": "William Pitt the Younger",
        "C": "Tony Blair",
        "D": "William Cavendish",
        "correct": "William Pitt the Younger"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the type of wood that God calls Noah to build the ark according to Genesis?",
        "A": "Moab",
        "B": "Cypress",
        "C": "Seraph",
        "D": "Zealots",
        "correct": "Cypress"
    }],
    "12": [{
        "question": "What was the only painting sold by Vincent van Gogh during his lifetime?",
        "A": "Sunflowers",
        "B": "The Starry Night",
        "C": "The Red Vineyard",
        "D": "The Yellow House",
        "correct": "The Red Vineyard"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Reina Sofia Art Center is located in what European city?",
        "A": "Madrid",
        "B": "Lisbon",
        "C": "Rome",
        "D": "Vienna",
        "correct": "Madrid"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of the following movies, to which did Johnny Depp not contribute with his acting?",
        "A": "Sweeney Todd",
        "B": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory",
        "C": "Finding Neverland",
        "D": "The Mask",
        "correct": "The Mask"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which nation won the World Championships in football in both 1930 and 1950?",
        "A": "Uruguay",
        "B": "Italy",
        "C": "Brazil",
        "D": "Hungary",
        "correct": "Uruguay"
    }],
    "13": [{
        "question": "Oysters can change something most other animals cannot. What is it?",
        "A": "Their Size",
        "B": "The thickness of their shell",
        "C": "Their Gender",
        "D": "Their color",
        "correct": "Their Gender"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do Steve Jobs, Bill Gates and Mark Zuckerberg have in common?",
        "A": "One of the parents is Ukrainian",
        "B": "Were adopted",
        "C": "Left the University",
        "D": "Have three children each",
        "correct": "Left the University"
    }],
    "14": [{
        "question": "Out of these European countries, which has the smallest population density?",
        "A": "Bulgaria",
        "B": "Norway",
        "C": "Iceland",
        "D": "France",
        "correct": "Iceland"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many points did Michael Jordan score on his first NBA game?",
        "A": "16",
        "B": "22",
        "C": "38",
        "D": "12",
        "correct": "16"
    },
    {
        "question": "A number one followed by one hundred zeros is known by what name?",
        "A": "Googol",
        "B": "Megatron",
        "C": "Gigabit",
        "D": "Nanomole",
        "correct": "Googol"
    },
    {
        "question": "In October 2021, a country outside Ukraine has recognized Ukrainian as the second official language. Where is this country?",
        "A": "Poland",
        "B": "France",
        "C": "Brazil",
        "D": "Portugal",
        "correct": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the second millennium begin?",
        "A": "on 1st January, 1000",
        "B": "on 1st January, 1001",
        "C": "on 1st January, 2000",
        "D": "on 1st January, 2001",
        "correct": "on 1st January, 1001"
    }]
}